# **Gaukas Wang**

Computer Engineer (B.Sc.)

Boulder, Colorado, USA

### Skills

| Software Development | 4+ yrs  |
|----------------------|---------|
| Linux System Admin   | 4+ yrs. |
| Cloud computing      | 3+ yrs. |
| Cybersecurity        | 2+ yrs. |
| Code Review          | 2+ yrs. |
| Embedded Systems     | 1+ yrs. |

### **Education**

Aug 2018 - May 2021

Electrical and Computer Engineering (B.Sc.)

University of Colorado Boulder

Summa Cum Laude, GPA: 3.93

# **Interests**

- Piano
- Cooking
- Fitness
- Handcraft
- Naval History

# Contact

- $\Box$  +1 720 366 4156
- gaukaswang@gmail.com
- github.com/Gaukas
- in linkedin.com/in/gaukaswang

# **Biography**

Yiyan Wang, a.k.a Gaukas Wang, is an Electrical & Computer Engineer with years of experiences in the field of Censorship Circumvention and Software Engineering. During his undergraduate study, he worked as teaching assistant, research assistant, as well as student researcher in the University of Colorado Boulder and made independent contribution to the research projects he worked on. Currently, Gaukas is working as a Software Engineer in Telecommunication industry and a Researcher in Censorship Circumvention. He will be pursuing a Ph.D. candidacy in the field of Computer Science Engineering starting the Fall semester in 2022.

# Work experience

#### **Software Engineer**

08/2021 - Today

IntelePeer

Develop, maintain and optimize the Voice Service portal/application which connects clients to the  $\mathsf{DID}/\mathsf{Toll}\text{-}\mathsf{Free}$  infrastructure.

#### Founder, Chief Technical Officer

08/2017 - Today

Tunnel.Work

Working as Software Engineer, DevOps, as well as Researcher here.

### Censorship Researcher, Software Engineer

01/2021 - Today

Refraction Networking (Prof. Eric Wustrow) University of Colorado Boulder

Improving a censorship circumventing system called Conjure by developing a new transport utilizing WebRTC.

### Research & Teaching Assistant

04/2020 - 04/2021

CU-NVM /Dept of ECEE (Prof. Joseph Izraelevitz) University of Colorado Boulder

- Conduct benchmarks on distributed system implementations and improve an existing RDMA-based broadcasting system.
- Assist in ECEN-4313/5033 (Concurrent Programming) and ECEN-1310 (C Programming for ECE).

### Research

- G. Wang & J. Wampler & E. Wustrow (est. 2022). "Peering into the Abyss: Using WebRTC in Censorship Circumvention".
- J. Izraelevitz & G. Wang & K. Silvers & G. Chockler & A. Gotsman (est. 2022). "Acuerdo, Fast Broadcast over RDMA".
- Z. Liu & D. Grunwald & J. Izraelevitz & G. Wang & S. Ha (EuroSys'22). "MTROM: Mostly Reliable Totally Ordered Multicast".

Signed on 17th October 2021

Yiyan "Gaukas" Wang